usana.com 2000-05-10

# USANA Inc. - Internet Privacy Policy

  |  | 

USANA’s Internet Privacy Policy

USANA respects the privacy of every individual who visits our web site, and we are strongly committed to protecting their personal information. Please take a moment to read the following policy statement to understand how USANA collects, uses and safeguards the personal information you provide to us on the website. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

**General Information about All USANA.COM Visitors**

As a visitor to USANA’s website, you are anonymous to the company. Like many other commercial websites, USANA may use a standard technology called a "cookie" that measures the number of visitors to the different sections of the website. Cookies are designed, generally, to collect and store the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (e.g., aol.com, if you are connecting from an American Online account), the date and time you access USANA’s site, and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to USANA’s site. USANA uses the information collected by cookies to improve its site and make it more useful to visitors. USANA’s cookies do not collect personal information. 

**Information about You**

Sometimes USANA may ask you to provide specific information about you when you sign up to use a service, like Downline Management, or when you order a product online. In this case, USANA needs certain information, such as name, internet and/or e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, credit card number, etc., in order to provide that service or product to you. When obtaining information from you, USANA will ask for only the information we need to provide the service or product you have requested. You may rest assured that USANA will never misuse the information you provide us. Moreover, USANA will attempt to keep your information complete, up-to-date, and accurate. 

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information**

Where permitted by applicable law, USANA may provide your personal information to certain third parties. For example, USANA may give your personal information to its authorized employees, directors, and managers to help the company develop internal reports, plan and facilitate meetings and training, and administer Distributor benefits. USANA may also provide your personal information to agents, contractors, suppliers, or vendors that offer administrative, advertising, printing, or other services to USANA for the benefit of its Distributors. Examples of such services include VOX voicemail, USANA One Long Distance, USANA Plus Credit Card, and personalized USANA checks. Finally, USANA may disclose your personal information to government agencies or regulatory authorities. Of course, USANA will never reveal your personal information to any third party without your prior knowledge and consent, unless the company is required to do so by law. __

**How to Contact USANA about Your Personal Information**

If you wish to verify that the personal information USANA has about you is correct or if you wish to have your name and/or e-mail address removed from any lists maintained by the company, you may contact USANA’s Distributor Service Department in writing at 3838 West Parkway Boulevard, Salt Lake City, Utah 84120-6336 or by e-mail message to [dist.serv@us.usana.com](mailto:dist.serv@us.usana.com). USANA will promptly respond to your questions or requests and correct any errors or inaccuracies in your personal information.
